<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our team on Purposeful Camp Namibia</title>
    <link>/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Our team on Purposeful Camp Namibia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2020 Purposelful Camp Namibia, All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ndakondja Uusiku: Founder and Chairperson</title>
      <link>/team/ndakondja/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/ndakondja/</guid>
      <description>Ndakondja Uusiku: Founder and Chairperson Ndakondja Uusiku is a 19-year-old accounting student at the Namibia University of Science and Technology. Ndakondja awaits to graduate from the Olafika SME Development and Mentoring Program with an accredited certificate in SME Development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jane Hango: Co-founder and Vice Chairperson</title>
      <link>/team/jane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/jane/</guid>
      <description>Jane Hango: Co-founder and Vice Chairperson Jane Hango is a 20-year-old Second Year Medical Student at UNAM Hage Geingob Campus, who is a proud product of Canisianum RCHS. She debated at national level for the Omusati region 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuilika Andreas: Co-founder and Project Coordinator</title>
      <link>/team/tuilika/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/tuilika/</guid>
      <description>Tuilika Andreas: Co-founder and Project Coordinator Tuilika Andreas is a second-year medical student at the University of Namibia. Apart from being an academic, she functions as an integral part of her society by being part of various organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paulina Hambata: Co-founder, Editor General and Public Relations Officer</title>
      <link>/team/paulina/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/paulina/</guid>
      <description>Paulina Hambata: Co-founder, Editor General and Public Relations Officer Paulina Hambata is a 19-year-old 2nd Year Medical Student at UNAM Hage Geingob Campus. She has been ranked at national level in JSC and regionally for NSSCH examinations during her high school career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Otto Anna: Course coordinator</title>
      <link>/team/ottoanna/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/ottoanna/</guid>
      <description>Otto Anna: Course coordinator Otto Anna is a 20-year-old Law Student at the University of Namibia (Unam). Anna is a young, in the making, motivational speaker who believes that all Black Children’s Dreams are possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bongumenzi Khumalo aka BJ: Head of Accommodation</title>
      <link>/team/bongumenzi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/bongumenzi/</guid>
      <description>Bongumenzi Khumalo aka BJ: Head of Accommodation Bongumenzi Siphiwosami Khumalo is a 19-year-old Swazi citizen (liswati) doing his Second year in Bachelor of Medicine at the University of Namibia Hage Geingob Campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nabot Tomas: Outdoor Coordinator</title>
      <link>/team/nabot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/nabot/</guid>
      <description>Nabot Tomas: Outdoor Coordinator Nabot Tomas is a 20-year-old second year student at the Medical school of Unam. He has been serving as a volunteer at Beautiful Kids Namibia since 2015 and is very passionate about working with the Youth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magano Kafula: Outdoor Coordinator</title>
      <link>/team/magano/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/magano/</guid>
      <description>Magano Kafula: Outdoor Coordinator Magano Kafula is a 20-year-old and second year Law student at the University of Namibia. She is currently the Communications Chairperson of Inspire Career Guidance, an organization which gives high school learners in the northern schools of Namibia information regarding university courses and bursary opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ainley Amunyela: Culinary Guru</title>
      <link>/team/ainley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/ainley/</guid>
      <description>Ainley Amunyela: Culinary Guru Ainley Amunyela is currently a student at the University of Namibia&amp;rsquo;s HGC campus studying towards a Bachelor’s Degree in Medicine and Surgery. She is the President of the Medical Students&amp;rsquo; Association of Namibia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prince Eelu: Course coordinator</title>
      <link>/team/prince/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/prince/</guid>
      <description>Prince Eelu: Course coordinator Prince Eelu is a Bachelor of Entrepreneurship student at Namibia University of Science and Technology. Co-founder of Mindaway Investments and as well a Business Development Consultant and Quantum House, a diversified group that incorporates various SMEs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mathews Kambuze: Head of Recreational activities</title>
      <link>/team/mathews/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/mathews/</guid>
      <description>Mathews Kambuze: Head of Recreational activities Mathews Kambuze is a 21-year-old young man. He is a God-fearing fellow with strong biblical values. He an excellent public speaking trainer, MC &amp;amp; facilitator.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>